克里夫·比克斯比
Clive Bixby.
多么性感的惊喜啊
What a sexy surprise.
快速问答
Quick question.
你从天堂坠落时疼吗
Did it hurt when you fell from heaven?
因为你
Because you--uh...
我重新来一次
I'm gonna come in again.
情人节我们得照看小宝贝乔
We are watching baby Joe on Valentine's Day
方便我爸和歌洛莉亚可以
so my dad and Gloria can...
-做爱 -恶 别这样
- Make love. - Ew. Don't.
重点是我们要提前一天庆祝节日
The point is, we are celebrating a day early.
好让他们有空亲热
So they can finally be intimate.
你 说得太多了
You've... more than made that point.
我只是说他们生完孩子后已经等很久了
I'm just saying it's a long wait after giving birth.
六周了
Six weeks.
我绝对没办法那么长时间不碰这位
I couldn't keep my hands off this one for that long.
我能想象杰该多痛苦
I can only imagine what Jay's going through.
瞧
Voila.
方结 真了不起
Square knot. Impressive.
我可以打各种各样的结
I can make any kind of knot.
就像我嘴里有位水手似的
It's like I have a sailor in my mouth.
我得打探一下孩子们的情况
I should check on the kids.
海莉带他们去看电影了 不会接的
Haley took 'em to a movie. She's not even gonna answer.
我知道 但是亲爱的 我没办法不担心
I know, but, sweetie, I have a good reason to worry.
卢克早上鼻血流得厉害
Luke had that nasty nosebleed this morning,
而艾丽克斯又一如既往地晕过去了
and Alex, as usual, fainted.
她没事的 而且邓菲家人容易流鼻血
She's fine, and Dunphy men get nosebleeds.
我结婚的时候就告诉你了 誓词中有说
I told you this when we got married. It was in my vows.
我还是有点不明白你为什么要在誓词中提这个
I'm still a little unclear as to why you put them in your vows--
快喝完那杯饮料吧 美女
Just finish that drink, pretty lady.
我们要赶着过漫漫春宵呢
We got a big night ahead of us.
好吧
Okay.
首先我们玩点儿风流浪漫
First, we have a date with romance.
3P 如果你愿意的话
A threesome, if you will.
接着我们将进行老式"飞船野餐"
From here, we move on to an old-fashioned blimpnic.
是那种男人面对着女人...
Now is that the one where the man has to face out at the woman...
在小飞船上野餐
It's a picnic on a blimp.
香槟 奶酪 美丽的城市尽收眼底
Champagne, cheese, and this beautiful city beneath us.
听起来真浪漫
That actually sounds really romantic.
之后我们摘下耳塞 换上御寒耳套
After that, we swap our earplugs for some earmuffs,
到溜冰场的月光下旋转飞舞
And take a few moonlit turns around the local ice rink.
接着 我们就迅速回到旅馆
From there, it's a quick trip back to the hotel,
-在那里 - 我觉得天旋地转
- where... - I'm spinning.
我可不想以此开场
Well, I wouldn't start with that,
但是 我们可以慢慢达到那种境界
but, uh, we--we can work our way up to it.
不是 我真的感觉不妙
No. I'm feeling really weird.
听到了吗 克里夫 告诉我你想要什么
Catch that, Clive? Just tell me what you want.
朱莉安娜
Juliana?
克莱尔
Claire?
你们俩得回答我一个啊
One of you needs to answer me.
血压还正常
Blood pressure's still good.
你可以回家了
I think I can send you home.
太好了 只是因为低血糖吗
Great. So it was probably just low blood sugar or something?
看吧 亲爱的 早就说没什么好担心的嘛
See, honey? I told you it was nothing to worry about.
不是没什么
Well, it's not nothing.
当时你确实有心动过速的情况
You did have a small heart episode.
科本医生 那可能是我的错
Dr. Coben, this may have been my fault.
我当时可能 太性感了
I think I was being... too sexy.
我不认为是那个问题
Yeah, I don't think that's an issue.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
医生 你的意思不是指
Um, doctor, you're not saying that
我是心脏病发作吧
I had a heart attack or something, right?
不是 只是非常轻微的心律不齐
Not at all. What you have is a very minor arrhythmia,
也就是常说的预激综合征
known as wolff-parkinson-white syndrome.
那是遗传性的 所以跟你没关系
It's hereditary, so you're off the hook.
对啊 我妈有这病
Oh, yeah. My mom has that.
我们会进行药物治疗
We'll treat it with medication
你们几天后再回来
and have you back in a couple of days.
同时 悠着点就行了
In the meantime, just take it easy.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you!
我们是不是该跟你爸说
I guess we should tell your dad
我们明天照顾不了宝宝了
we can't watch the baby tomorrow.
不行 不行
No. No.
我不想让别人知道
I don't want everyone to know about this.
他们会担心的
They're just gonna get worried
然后小题大做
and--and make a bigger deal of it than it is.
亲爱的 答应我
Sweetheart, promise me?
好啦我答应 我知道不是什么大事
I promise. I know it's not that big a deal.
那是非常大的事
This is a huge deal...
我绝对要负一点责任
for which I'm partly responsible,
不管克莱尔的拉拉医生怎么说
in spite of what Claire's lesbian doctor says.
亲爱的 我在看这种病的相关资料
Hey, honey, I was just reading about this wolff-white thing.
没那么严重 你会没事的
It's not that serious. You're gonna be fine.
我知道
I know.
有人想去滑冰吗
Who's ready to hit the ice?
-什么 -拜托
- What? - Come on.
有人答应我去月下滑冰的
Somebody promised me a moonlit skate.
但医生不是让你悠着点吗
But didn't the doctor say you needed to take it easy?
他们总是这样说啦
Oh, that's just one of those things they have to say,
比如怀孕的时候别喝酒
Like, "You can't drink when you're pregnant."
拜托 我们不能白白浪费了情人节啊
Come on. We're not gonna seriously blow off valentine's day,
对吧
are we?
不 我只是想为什么 要去溜"冰"
No. I just thought why... ice things down
我们可以好好亲"热"
when we could heat things up?
-我喜欢这样 -是吗
- Oh, I like where this is going. - Right?
-是啊 -是吗
- Yes. - Yeah?
是 不
Ye--no!
亲爱的 我知道你要干嘛
Honey, I know what you're doing.
你把我当成个病人
You're treating me like a patient,
-但你答应过我不会这样的 -不
- and you promised that you wouldn't. - No.
不不不 我想到了个更好的点子
No, no, no, no, no. I just had a better idea.
什么
What?
肩并肩夫妻按摩
Side-by-side couples massage.
只有你和我 以及几个柬埔寨人
Just you, me, and a couple Cambodian guys
让我们全身爽翻天
to work us over good.
真具体
Specific.
什么声音
What is that?
是孩子们回家了吗
You think the kids are home?
好像不止我们家那三个
That sounds like more than our three.
他们以为我们不在家 就开派对了
They think we're not home, and they're having a party.
-我要杀了他们 -不不不 不不不
- I'm killing them. - No, no, no. No, no, no.
首先 应该由我去杀了他们
"A"--it's my turn to kill them.
其次 你还得打电话叫按摩师
"B"--you need to order up those massages.
在"顶尖美国可口可乐好时光按摩所"下面
It's under "Best number one U.S.A. Coca-cola good time massage."
搞什么玩意儿啊
What the hell is going on?!
爸 你怎么在家
Dad? What are you doing home?
你们就这样吗
So this is how it is?
我们前脚出门 你们后脚就搞起了派对
We're gone for a minute, and you guys throw a party?
没有
No!
刚给妈发短信说我们在电影院玩得很爽
Just texted mom we're having a good time at the movies.
每回都有效
It works every t--aah!
-居然还经常这么搞 -没有
- So this is a regular thing? - No!
你们都很熟悉了吧 凉饮在后 面
You know the drill. Coolers our b--aah--ack!
够了 把音响关掉
Enough! Turn off the music!
不是我生的 立刻给我滚出去
Everybody who I did not create, get out of my house right now!
我不想生气
I don't want to get upset.
我今晚已经够难受的了
I've been through enough tonight.
-出什么事了 -我不该告诉你们的
- What happened? - I'm not supposed to tell you.
你这么说 我们只会更乱想
When you say it like that, we make it worse in our head.
好吧 不是什么大事
Fine. It's no big deal.
你们的妈妈进了趟医院
Your mother had to go to the hospital.
-天呐 -什么
- Oh, my god! - What?!
那比我们乱想的还要糟糕
That is so much worse than it would be in our heads!
她没事 只是昏倒了一会
She's fine. She just passed out a little.
心脏出了点毛病
Something to do with her heart.
-难道是心脏病发作 -妈妈心脏病发作了
- Like a heart attack?! - Mom had a heart attack?!
-妈妈几乎心脏病发作死了 -不是
- Mom almost died of a heart attack?! - No!
她心脏出了点小毛病 很可能是我引发的
She had a little episode, probably triggered by me.
她休息休息就好了
She just needs to rest.
就这一次 我们别只想着我们自己
For once, let's not think about ourselves.
菲尔 没什么事吧
Phil, everything okay?
没事 我来了
Fine! I'm coming!
都表现正常点
Just act like everything's normal.
如果来了两个柬埔寨人
Oh, and if, uh, two Cambodian guys show up,
让他们去我们卧室
Send them to our bedroom.
孩子们请了几个朋友来玩
Kids had a few friends over.
我都搞定了
I handled it.
你很擅长"搞"定事情嘛
So you're good at handling things.
喜欢不
You like?
我爱死了 但穿这做按摩不太合适吧
Me love, but is this appropriate massage wear?
他们很忙的 我们也该"忙"起来
They were busy, which is what we should be getting.
亲爱的
Honey.
亲爱的 你确定心脏承受得住吗
Honey, are you sure this is okay for your--aah!
咸咸的
Salty.
我技巧"咸"熟着呢
I still have a few moves.
是薯片的咸味 亲爱的
Mm, that's the chips, sweetie.
-对不住 -没事儿
- Oh, sorry. - Right.
妈 我们需要和你谈谈
Mom, we need to talk to you.
爸让我们什么都别说
Dad told us not to say anything,
但我们真的很担心你
But we're really worried about you.
-你告诉他们了 -没有
- You told them?! - No!
你心脏病发作了
You had a heart attack?
-菲尔 -我可不是这么说的
- Phil! - That is not what I said.
孩子们 一切都很好
Kids, everything is fine.
-快打911 -上帝
- Call 9-1-1! - Oh, god!
她的心脏爆炸了
Her heart exploded!
我的天 我又害了你
Oh, my god! I did it again!
菲尔 是你的鼻血
Phil, it's your nose!
我就这么一个要求
This is the one thing--
我就这么一个要求 让你别小题大做
The one thing I ask from you is not to make a big deal of this,
你却连这都做不到
And you couldn't even do that.
亲爱的 你得保持冷静
Honey, you need to stay calm.
不 我不用 我好得很
No, I don't, because I am fine.
我们都很好
We are all fine.
-我的天 -海莉 弄醒你的妹妹
- Oh, god. - Haley, revive your sister.
没心情听你道歉 菲尔
Not in the mood for an apology, Phil.
很好 我也没打算道歉
Good, 'cause you're not gettin' one.
我有权担心你
I'm allowed to worry about you.
是没错 但总得有担心的事出现吧
Yeah, when there's something to worry about.
但这压根没事 我跟你说了 我妈也这样
But this was nothing. I told you, my mom has this.
但我却今天才知道
Which I just found out about today.
为什么过去20年都没这样
How has that not come up in 20 years?
我到...年纪了呗
I was... getting to it.
我知道你总觉得
Look, I know you feel like
自己该是家里的顶梁柱
you have to be the rock for this family
女儿男朋友的事 儿子流鼻血的事
and worry about everybody's boy problems and nosebleeds
蔬菜吃得够不够
And... who has enough greens.
蔬菜就得占到半盘子
They're supposed to cover half the plate.
克莱尔 别这样了
Claire, stop it.
我是说你可以让我们来照顾你
I'm saying you could let us take care of you
时不时的
every once in a while.
比如 你心脏不好晕倒的时候
Like for example, when you clutch your chest and collapse.
你柔弱一下子
This house isn't gonna crumble in the dust
房子又不会就塌了
if you let yourself be vulnerable.
那可说不准
We don't know that.
我们可以试一试
We could find out.
我当时是有点害怕
It was kind of scary.
我知道
Of course.
-但我一知道是什么就... -别毁氛围
- Until I knew what it was, and then-- - Don't ruin it.
我还有一个问题
I just have one more question.
当时疼吗
Did it hurt?
我还没怎么感觉就昏过去了
Well, I blacked out before I--
当你从天堂坠落的时候
When you fell from heaven?
成功
Nailed it.
你照顾好克莱尔 乔我们自己来
You just take care of Claire. We got Joe.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
在 我的爱人
Si, mi amor?
情人节快...
Happy valentine's--
等等 等等 先停一下
Wait. Wait. Wait. Time-out.
菲尔刚来电话 他们今天没法照顾乔了
That was Phil. They can't watch Joe today.
克莱尔昨天进了急诊室
Claire was in the emergency room last night.
-她还好吗 -她没事
- Is she okay? - She's gonna be fine,
-但你懂的 她有点... -那就行
- But, you know, she had a little bit-- - Okay, good.
你穿这套西装真是帅呆了
I love how you look in this suit.
把它脱掉扔地板上看看怎么样 行不
Let's see how it looks on the floor, okay?
好吧 但我一小时后要去开会
Okay, but I gotta be in a meeting in one hour.
你真是傻得可爱 都六周没做了
Ay, that's so cute that after six weeks,
你竟然觉得你还能持续一小时
you think you're going to need an hour!
情人节快乐
Happy valentine's day!
一年中就这么一天
It's the one time of the year
全世界的人都想和平常的我一样浪漫
when the world tries to be as romantic as I am all the time.
-祝好运 世界 -滚出去
- Good luck, world. - Get out.
既然你都快帮杰穿好衣服了
Anyway, since you're almost done dressing Jay...
我们今天就早点去学校吧
How about we head to school early?
我再去梳下头 我们车里见
I'll check my hair and meet you in the car.
歌洛莉亚 我最多2小时后就回来
Gloria, I'll be back in two hours, tops.
我们等你回来时 再决定体位 动作等问题
We decide who does what when you come back.
我因为闯红灯收到一张罚单
I got a ticket running a red light...
我们好歹让我被罚得值 把孩子放下
So let's make this worth it. Put the kid down.
我不能 他现在是个典型的普里契特
I can't. He's being a real Pritchett.
我们不能用我的姓来代指臭脾气
We need to come up with a different term for that.
瞧好了
Watch.
好吧 我以前有台电视接收信号也是时断时续
Okay, I used to have a TV got reception like that.
我来试试 乔乔 嘿 小家伙
Let me try. Hey, Joe Joe. Hey buddy.
男人之间悄悄说
Guy to guy,
你现在有点阻碍我的好事哦 你知道的
you're blocking me a little bit. You know that.
你知道的 你知道的 乔
Yes, you do. Yes, you do, Joe.
睡半小时怎么样 你觉得如何 小兄弟
Hey, how about a half-hour? What do you say, pal? Huh?
你能做到吗
Can you do it?
乖宝宝
Attaboy!
你从未像此刻这般令我心动
I've never been more attracted... to you.
证明给我看
Prove it.
-你们在接吻吗 -你可真会毁气氛
- Are you kissing? - That's a bit of a mood killer.
我大爸二爸也经常接吻
My daddies kiss a lot.
彻底毁了
And flatlined.
米奇和小卡要办个情人节派对
Mitch and Cam are having a party for valentine's.
克莱尔本来是要照顾她的
Claire was supposed to take care of her,
但她现在没法照顾了
but now she can't.
莉莉 我们真高兴你来玩
Lily, we're so happy to have you here.
我为你准备了一个大惊喜哦
I have a big surprise for you!
瞧 一个崭新的电视遥控器
Look! A brand-new, shiny TV remote!
看上去好复杂哦
Looks complicated.
你就随便乱按 总会有好节目出现的
Just keep hitting all those buttons until something good happens.
反正我就是打算那样做的
That's my plan, anyway.
怎么现在都来搅局啊
Where were all these distractions
我们造出乔的那晚他们怎么不来啊
the night that Joe was conceived?
我开玩笑的 他是个天赐的礼物
I'm kidding. He's a blessing.
请问有何贵干
Can I help you?
你好 我叫哈伦 我是来安装婴儿防护的
Yeah, I'm Harlan. I'm here to do your baby proofing.
杰 我等这个预约已经等了几星期了
Jay, I've been waiting for this appointment for weeks.
我的"预约"等得更久
I've waited longer for mine.
人类安然无恙地存活一千多年了
The human race has survived for a thousand years
都没用到这些泡沫保险杠和婴儿防护门
without these foam bumpers and--and gates everywhere.
老天 我以前开车去超市
Hell, I used to drive to the supermarket
米奇尔和克莱尔就坐在引擎盖上
with Mitchell and Claire on the hood of the car.
什么时候大家都变得这么过度保护了
When did everybody get so overprotective?
或许就从孩子们从车上飞出去开始
Maybe when kids started flying off cars.
需要多久
How long?
通常我会有个帮手 但是戴尔...
Normally I have help, but Dale, uh...
你之前在店里见过戴尔 他是个大高个
You met Dale at the shop. He's a tall guy.
-他是我姐姐的孩子 -听着
- He's my sister's kid-- - Hey, listen.
你和我要在1小时内把这些都装好
You and I are gonna bang this out in about an hour.
你想装在哪儿
Where do you want it?
我知道很多人都认为我喜欢杰
I know a lot of people think that I'm attracted to Jay
是因为他的钱 但他们都错了
because of his money, but they're wrong.
我被他吸引 是因为他很性感
I'm attracted to him because he's sexy,
他今天更是性感爆棚
And he's never been sexier than today.
那身西装
The suit...
扛盒子时威武雄壮的样子
The carrying of the boxes...
不不 你给我听好了
No, no. You listen to me.
我妻子的车已经送过去4天了
You've had my wife's car four days.
检查出那尖锐的摩擦声是怎么回事
Figure out what that screeching noise is,
否则我就打得你尖叫不止
or you'll be making one yourself.
对着电话霸气的训斥
The yelling on the phone...
给我
Give me that.
以及"钻孔"的样子
And the drilling.
"钻"得"好深好深"
So much drilling.
你该走了 哈伦
Time to go, Harlan.
好的 你需要我给你讲解一下...
Okay. You want me to walk you through any of the--
-不用了 我们自己来吧 -好吧 听着
- No, we'll take it from here. - Okay. Uh, listen.
如果防护门出现问题 你们就给我打个电话
Give me a call if you have any trouble with the gates,
因为那些门有时候不太好用
because they're a little tricky, you know?
你们用的时候一定要轻轻的
You gotta be gentle with it.
10秒钟 否则你不来我也"开工"了
Ten seconds, or I start without you.
不管你准备好没有 我这就...
Ready or not, here I...
快开啊
Come on!
你必须得往上抬一下
Okay, you have to lift it.
那不是抬的 是往里面挤的
It's not a lift. It's a squeeze.
好吧 那你就挤啊
Okay, then squeeze it!
我正在挤呢 根本打不开
I'm squeezing it! It's impossible!
杰 拜托
Jay, please.
我最开心的一天
Best day ever!
我刚被一个暗恋我的人邀请参加情人节派对
I just got invited to a valentine's party by a secret admirer!
-你应该去 -听着好棒啊 快去
- You should go. - Sounds great! Go!
我显然得盛装打扮一番
I obviously need to get dressed first.
你能控制在半小时以内吗
Can you keep it under a half-hour?
你真搞笑
You're funny.
曼尼 快点 快走吧
Manny, come on. Let's go!
放轻松
Relax.
你不需要开车送我去 就在街尾
You don't have to drive me. It's just down the street.
我以为我 必须要送你呢
Oh, I thought I... had to drive you.
你干嘛戴顶帽子
What's with the hat?
我的暗恋者要求
My secret admirer requested
我戴一顶有羽毛的帽子
I wear a hat with a feather in it.
我就在想 哪顶啊
I'm like, "Which one?"
是吗
Really?
那个暗恋者有其他要求吗
This secret admirer have any other requests?
是的
Uh, yes.
她还让我准备些诗歌 在派对上吟诵
She asked me to bring some poetry to recite at the party.
那些 参加派对的孩子
These, uh, kids at the party...
他们应该不是那些受欢迎的孩子吧
they wouldn't be the popular ones by any chance?
都是最受欢迎的红人 怎么了
The most popular. Why?
没什么 你 玩得开心
No reason. Just... Have fun.
我会的
I will.
不 杰
No, Jay.
需要往里面挤
It's squeeze.
怎么 我有口臭吗
What? I have cigar breath?
不是你的原因
It's not you.
难道你已经射...
Ay. Did you already...
什么
What?
不是
No!
不 我是担心曼尼
No. I'm worried about Manny.
我觉得他正步入一个陷阱
I think he's being set up for
在派对上会大出洋相的
some kind of humiliation at that party.
你为他担心 真是个好父亲的样子
Oh. That's so sweet of you to worry.
我之前以为你的性感已经到顶 无法再突破了呢
Just when you thought that you couldn't get any sexier.
-他会没事的 对吧 -嗯 他会没事的
- Yeah, he's fine, right? - Yeah, he's fine.
快过来
Come here...
我觉得我得去看看他
Oh, I think I gotta check on him.
他说有个什么暗恋他的人
There was something about some kind of secret admirer
-让他... -带上他写的诗是吧
- getting him to... - Bring his poems?
我给他的上衣除毛时他跟我说了
Yeah, he told me when I was lint-rolling his jacket.
难道你不担心那是个恶作剧吗
And you're not worried it's a prank?
我当然担心了
Of course I worry.
我总是为他担心
I worry about him all the time.
但就像你说的
But like you said,
我们没法保护他们免受一切伤害
we can't protect them from everything.
所以我是在试着 放开一点
So I'm just trying to, like, let go a little bit.
让他坐在车顶上吗
Let him ride on top of the car?
不 那太疯狂了
No, that's just crazy.
那是最难的一点 不是吗
That's the hardest part, isn't it?
当你意识到你无法阻止这个世界伤害他们
When you realize you can't stop the world from hurting them.
你说得我好想哭
Now you're making me want to cry.
今天不该这样的
This is not what this day is all about.
你说得对
You're right.
好
Okay.
我去给我们拿点香槟来
I'll go and get us some champagne.
好主意
Good idea.
曼尼
Manny?
不 没事
No, nothing.
我就是想问问你还好吗
Just wanted to know if everything is okay.
喂 乖女儿 抱歉打扰你
Hi, honey. Sorry to bother you.
我知道你在休息
I know you're resting.
我听说你昨晚晕倒了
I heard you had a little scare last night.
你什么时候再去看医生
Hey, uh, when are you going back to the doctor?
如果你愿意 我可以陪你一起去
'cause if you want, I can go with you.
今年的情人节
This year for Valentine's Day,
我们决定给所有的单身朋友
we decided to throw a lonely hearts party
办场"孤心派对"
for all of our single friends.
有时在他们周围
Sometimes when we're around them,
我们会为自己找到了真命天子而内疚
we feel a little guilty for having found each other,
就好像我们对着他们的脸甩幸福似的
like we're waving our love in their faces.
你非要说得让人想歪吗
There's gotta be a better way of saying that.
总之 我们本来打算办场高雅的派对
Anyway, it was supposed to be an elegant affair.
瞧我的媚眼
Ogle me.
好戏要开始咯 把猫拿走
Showtime. Put the cat away.
好的 好的
Okay. Yeah. Great.
-对了 米奇尔 -怎么了
- Oh, and, Mitchell, please... Hey. - Yeah?
今晚你要放开了好好玩儿
Please try to have fun tonight.
我一直都很放得开啊
I always have fun.
不 我知道你很擅长宅在家里玩儿
No, I know you're great at stay-at-home fun
或是窝在沙发里玩儿
and sit-on-the-couch fun,
但这是派对狂欢 而你有时...
but this is party fun, and sometimes you--
行了 这样可不好玩
Okay, this is not fun.
去开门
Get the door.
让小哥我放开玩给你看
I will show you some fun.
那之后的事情就有点记不清了
Things got a little hazy after that.
喂
Hello?
爸 你好
Yeah, hi--hi, dad.
不不 我起来了 起来了
No, no. I'm up. I am up.
好 送她过来吧 随时都行
Yeah, bring her by at any time.
好 晚安
Okay. Good night.
小卡
Oh, Cam.
天呐 昨晚还真是疯狂的派对啊
Oh, god, that was some party last night.
是啊 我很高兴你安全回来了
Yeah. Well, I'm just glad you made it home safely.
什么 回来 我不...
Wha--made--made it ho-- I don't--
我都不记得我离开过
I don't even remember leaving the party.
我好像是有点微醺
Oh, I-I think I got a little tipsy.
微醺
Tipsy?
你比《广告狂人》里的人喝得都醉
You were like all of the "Mad Men."
不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
别弄得就跟我有多疯狂 多失控似的
Don't make it out like I did a lot of crazy, out of control--
我以为那是我梦中的情景呢
I was hoping I dreamt that.
行啦 就跟你没有在喝高之后
Come on. Like--like you've never had a few cocktails
用樱桃酒把猫染成粉色过似的
and died a cat pink with cherry Kool-Aid.
好吧 还有什么别的需要告诉我的吗
Okay. Well, is there anything else you need to tell me about?
我不记得有什么了
Not that I remember.
现在记起这事了
I'm remembering this.
天呐 米奇尔
Oh, my gosh, Mitchell,
那是伯特和道迪·温切尔家的
are these Burt and Dottie Winchell's
圣诞节装饰物吗 你怎么能这样
Christmas decorations? How could you?
他们到现在都没收起来
They never take them down, okay?
我这是给整个社区做了件好事
I was doing the whole neighborhood a favor.
天呐
Oh, god.
小卡 我觉得...好像还拍了照片
Cam, I... You know, I think-- I-I think there are pictures.
我记得胡娇和朗吉娜...好吧
I remember Pepper and Longinus were--okay.
天呐 可怜的小驯鹿
Oh, my gosh. Those poor reindeer.
似乎"欢腾"才是派对之花啊
Oh, it seems like Prancer is the belle of the ball--
不出意料
No surprise there.
你一定就是"悍妇"咯
Oh. You must be Vixen.
行了行了 这不好笑 米奇尔
Okay. Okay. Not funny, Mitchell.
瞧瞧我们家 你脑子进水了吧
Look at this place. What were you thinking?
小卡 我 我是有点疯狂过度了
Okay. Cam, I... Yes, I went a little nuts, all right?
我很抱歉
I-I'm sorry.
但我没做任何不能挽回的事啊
But I didn't do anything that can't be undone.
早啊室友们
Hey, roomies.
真的很感谢你们让我搬来住
Hey, thank you so much for letting me move in here.
好 能让我们先单聊
Yes. Could you excuse us for just a...
一会儿吗 迪兰
a moment, Dylan?
好 尽管聊别着急
Yeah. Take as much time as you need.
这是你们家 我只是住在这里而已
It's your house. I just live here now.
小卡 是我让他住进来的吗
Cam, did--did I tell him that he could live with us?
-显然啊 -天呐
- Obviously. - Oh, my god.
他参加我们的派对了吗
Was he even at our party?
是的 他在某个公司做豪华轿车司机
Yes. He's been driving a limousine for some company,
耶玛库斯昨晚雇了他
and J'marcus hired him for the night,
现在他搬来这里住了 你想起来没有
and now he lives here. Are you all caught up there?
我一点都不记得了
I-I don't remember any of this.
那我们来创造新的记忆吧
Well, let's create a new memory--
你去告诉他 他不能住这里
One where you tell him he can't live here.
我能说句话吗
Can I say one short thing?
昨晚来到这里时我心灰意冷
I came to this house a broken man
我妈妈为了她的新男友把我赶出了家
after my mom threw me out for her new boyfriend.
后来我又发现
And then I found out
轿车公司要开除我
I was getting let go from the limo company
与此同时海莉又抛下我去参加派对
the same night Haley goes to a party without me.
我一无所有 无依无靠
So I had nothing and no one.
而你们
And then you...
赶紧的 告诉他
Okay. Come on. Tell him.
让他说完
Let him finish.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道 同性恋们总是对我很好
I mean, gay dudes have always been nice to me--
超级好
I mean, super nice.
但从没有像你们这样的
But nothing like this.
我想我要说的是
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
天呐 他要开唱了吗
Oh, my god. He's gonna sing.
*多年来 凄凄惨惨地活着*
*So many years living life underwater*
*终于在 令媛的房间找到人间温暖*
*Came up for air in the room of your daughter*
*我从未想过 我会在*
*I never knew I would find my answer*
*前女友舅舅家里找到答案*
*In my ex-girlfriend's uncles' house*
*有一只小小的粉色美洲豹相伴*
*With the tiny pink panther*
迪兰 迪兰 打断下
Dylan, Dylan. I'm--I'm sorry.
我的天 这真是
Oh, gosh, I--this is...
这真是太难说出口了
This is really hard for me to say,
但我们不能
but we--we just cannot...
不去把猫洗一下
Not wash our cat.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我喝醉了那样对它 它一下也没抓我
And yet when I did that drunk, not a scratch.
我的天 比我们刚搬进来时还要干净
Oh, my gosh, this place is cleaner than when we moved in.
他是史上最好的房客
Best houseguest ever.
不行 不能收留他
No, we are not keeping him.
你觉得他把圣诞装饰送回温切尔家了吗
Do you think he took the christmas decorations back to the Winchell's?
我想他自以为这样做了
Oh, well, I think he thinks he did.
-什么 -是的
- What? - Okay, yeah.
-迪兰 -迪兰
- Dylan! - Dylan!
-迪兰 -不 不要
- Dylan! - No, no, no!
伙计们 我在上面
Oh, hey, guys. I'm up here.
是的 听着 迪兰
Yeah, hi. Listen, Dylan,
那些装饰是放在院子里的
those decorations were on the yard...
那家的院子
Of that house.
这样啊 想做好事变坏事了
Oh. No good deed, huh?
喂 从这里可以看到我们的家
Hey! I can see our house from here.
-老天 开什么玩笑 -迪兰 迪兰
- Oh, jeez. Are you kidding me? - Dylan! Dylan!
今天什么鬼日子
This day...
就住一晚 等他骨头稍微长好点
One night. Just till his bone sets.
但总会有各种理由让你不忍心对他开口
But there's always gonna be a reason not to tell him,
不是吗
isn't there?
好吧 我们不如这样
Okay. What if we, um--
不行 不行 不行
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
没我什么事 你自己铺的烂摊子自己收拾[躺]
No "We." You made your bed. You lie in it.
别躺在这里 我刚铺好
Don't lie there. I just made it.
抱歉
Sorry.
我没看 我没看
Not looking. Not looking.
进来吧 迪兰
It's okay, Dylan.
我给你们做了汤
I made you guys some soups.
迪兰 这么客气做什么
Oh, Dylan, you didn't have to do that.
小卡也不用这么客气主动收留我
Well, Cam didn't have to offer to let me stay here,
但他这样做了
but he did.
好好喝汤吧
So here are soups.
小卡主动收留
Cam offered?
我知道他是代表你们两个人说的
Well, I know he was speaking for both of you.
你当时还没回家 这样有问题吗
You weren't home yet. Is that a problem?
我没问题
Not for me.
迪兰 你能让我们单独待会儿吗
Dylan, can you give us just a moment?
我没看 我没看
Not looking. Not looking.
我去开
I'll get it!
我想某种程度上
So I guess in a way,
我们都有责任
we're both responsible.
是的 但仔细分析 责任是你的
Yeah, but in the real way, you're responsible.
快去搞定
Take care of that.
快去
Come on.
勇敢去吧
Let's do it.
我的天 我现在好恨我自己
Oh, my god. I hate myself right now.
什么样的禽兽
What kind of monster
会把受伤的无知小青年赶上大街
throws an injured innocent onto the street?
你不能住在这里 快出去
You can't live here. Get out!
-莉莉 -莉莉
- Lily. - Lily.
这样很奇怪 你是个大男生
It's weird. You're a big boy.
-抱歉 迪兰 -她不是有心的
- I'm sorry, Dylan. - She doesn't mean that.
不 她是对的 大家都这样说
No. She's right. Everyone says it.
我不能再逃避矛盾了
I need to stop running from conflict.
是时候做个勇敢的大男生 解决问题
It's time to be a big boy and patch things up
搬回我妈家去了
and move back in with my mom.
我去收拾东西
I'll get my things.
-好吧 抱歉 -抱歉
- Okay. Sorry. - Sorry.
我这么容易就脱身了
I guess I got off easy.
她说话很直接却超级有效
She is blunt but effective.
或许我们该派她去跟园丁谈谈
Maybe we should have her talk to the gardener.
小卡
Cam, um...
你真的觉得我这人很无趣吗
Do you really think that I'm not any fun?
-什么 -昨晚你说我...
- What? - Last night, you said that I--
我家可不是酒店
This isn't a hotel!
你已经说得很明白了 亲爱的
Yeah, you made your point, honey!
他已经懂了
He's got it.
不 我昨晚那样狂喝
No, it--I only drank like that last night
只是因为我想变得更有趣
because I... I was trying to be more fun.
不 我不是那个意思
Oh. No, I didn't mean it like that.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你知道我有派对前焦虑症 我很紧张
You know I have party anxiety. I was nervous.
不 你并没有完全说错
No, but you're not entirely wrong.
我的确可以少一些 端架子
I mean, I-I could be a little... less uptight
多放开一点
and loosen up a little bit.
对 也许我们可以
Yeah. Maybe we could, you know,
追求中庸的乐趣
aim for middle-ground fun.
如果你想重新庆祝下情人节
You know, if--if you're up for a do-over,
我最近听说了一种玩法
I recently heard of an idea
可以让我们享受下
that could put us in the low end
比中庸稍高档次的乐趣
of upper middle-ground fun.
好的
Okay.
你相信一见钟情吗
Do you believe in love at first sight,
还是我要再走进来一次
or should I walk in again?
-杰 -来了 亲爱的 我的妈呀
- Jay? - Coming, honey! Oh, god.
你在这里啊 杰 我还以为你醒不来了
There you are, Jay. I thought you'd never wake up.
我与暗恋我的女生共度的一晚
Turns out my night with my secret admirer
真是太完美了
couldn't have gone better.
我们整晚跳舞 最棒的地方就是
We danced all night. And the best part was,
-她的眼睛... -曼尼 曼尼
- Her eyes were just... - Manny. Manny, manny--
我超级想听
Dying to hear it.
等十秒钟进来告诉我和你妈
Wait ten seconds and come in and tell both of us.
杰 怎么去了这么久
Jay, you took so long.
我还没"玩完"呢
I'm not done with you.
我也跟你"没完"
I'm not done with you, either.
史上最棒的情人节派对
Best valentine's party ever.
有个女生
So there's this girl--
我还是从头开始讲吧
I should start from the beginning.
-好吧 -先交待下故事背景
- All right. - So first a little history...